A Guide to the Virginia Dietetic Association Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- American Dietetic Association: Draft on the Professional Standards of Practice, 1997, TD(17) (Box-folder 063:005)
- American Dietetic Association Annual Report, 1997, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 063:006)
- American Dietetic Association: ADA Positions/FANSA Statements, 19985, TD(9) (Box-folder 063:007)
- American Dietetic Association Report: "Affiliates and DPGs Role within the American Dietetic Association Strategic Plan", 1999, TD(6) (Box-folder 063:008)
- American Dietetic Association: Journal and Newsletter, 2004, Journals(2), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 063:009)
- American Dietetic Association: Handbook for State Public Relation, 1972, TD(102) (Box-folder 064:001)
  Handbook(1)
- American Dietetic Association: Media Relations Tips, 1985-1997, TD(102) (Box-folder 064:002)
  Reports, Journal Articles, State Media Representative Activity Reports
- American Dietetic Association: Media Representatives Public Relations Handbook, 1989(February), TD(84) (Box-folder 064:003)
- American Dietetic Association: Media Representatives Public Relations Handbook, 1989(June), TD(41) (Box-folder 064:004)
- American Dietetic Association: Media Representatives Public Relations Handbook, 1989(December), TD(41) (Box-folder 064:005)
- American Dietetic Association: Media Representatives Public Relations Handbook, 1990(February), TD(32) (Box-folder 064:006)
- American Dietetic Association: Media Representatives Public Relations Handbook, 1993, TD(145), Slides(66) (Box-folder 064:007)
- American Dietetic Association Campaign: The ABC's of Children's Nutrition, 1991, TD(17), Pamphlets(2), Flyers(2) (Box-folder 065:001)
- American Dietetic Association: Survey of American Dietary Habits, 1991, TD(19), Booklet(1), Photos(3) (Box-folder 065:002)
  Newspaper Releases, Reports
- American Dietetic Association: Nutrition and Health Campaign for Women, 1993, TD(52), Poster(1), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 065:003)
  Flyers, Publication Order Forms, News Releases
- American Dietetic Association: Child Nutrition and Health Campaign, 1995, TD(31), Slide(1), Journal(1), Poster(1) (Box-folder 065:004)
- American Dietetic Association: National Nutrition Month Event Planning Kit, 1999, Paphlet(1), Diskette(1), TD(2) (Box-folder 065:005)
- American Dietetic Association: ADAPAC Award of Excellence, 2003, TD(20) (Box-folder 065:006)
  Letters, Memorandum, Nomination Forms
- American Dietetic Association Workshop Presentation: "Economic Costs and Benefits of Nutrition Services", 1988, TD(55), Slides(64) (Box-folder 066:001)
- American Dietetic Association Workshop Presentation: "The Power of Persuation: Dialogue for Dollars", 1992, TD(160), Newsletter(1), Pamphlets(4) (Box-folder 066:002)
- American Dietetic Association Workshop Presentation: "Winning the Managed Care Game", 1994, TD(113), AD(2), Pamphlets(3), Slides(77) (Box-folder 066:003)
- American Dietetic Association Workshop Presentation: Marketing MNT to MCOS, 1995, TD(68), Newsletter(1), Journal Article(1), Booklets(3) (Box-folder 067:001)
  Order Forms
- American Dietetic Association Workshop Presentation: "Olean-An Exciting New Fat Replacer That Makes Great Tasting, Reduced-Fat and Reduced-Calories Foods" 1997, Slides(48) (Box-folder 067:002)
- American Dietetic Association Member Campaing Toolkit: Your Link to Nutrition and Health, 1998, TD(44), CD(1), Pamphlet(1), Flyers(5) (Box-folder 067:003)
- American Dietetic Association: ADA Public Policy Workshop, 2000, TD(28), AD(14), Booklet(1), Program Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 067:004)
  Reports, Letters, Memoranda, Registration Lists
- American Dietetic Association: IFC/ADA Gallup Survey, "How Are Americans Making Food Choices?", 1990, VHS Tape(1) (Box-folder 068:001)
- American Dietetic Association: Public Policy B-Roll with Lewin Data, 1997, VHS Tape(1) (Box-folder 068:002)
- American Dietetic Association: Kid's Nutrition PSA:"Gimme Five", 1999, VHS Tape(1) (Box-folder 068:003)
- American Dietetic Association: Talk on Nutrition at ON with Bonnie Land and Jay Brinkley, N.D., VHS Tape(1) (Box-folder 068:004)
- Southwest Dietetic Association: DAD Program, 1961 - 1962, TD(2), Flyer(1), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 069:001)
- Roanoke Dietetic Association: Completed DAD Forms, 1990, TD(128) (Box-folder 069:002)
- Roanoke Dietetic Association: Completed DAD Forms, 1991, TD(109) (Box-folder 069:003)
- Roanoke Dietetic Association: Completed DAD Forms, 1992, TD(95), AD(9), Namecard(1) (Box-folder 069:004)
  Memoranda, Letters
- American Dietetic Association: Completed DAD Forms, 1990-93, TD(10) (Box-folder 069:005)
- American Dietetic Association: Scrapbook, 1937-1940, Pamphlets(6), Newspaper clippings, TD(11), AD(2) (Box-folder 070:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association Scrapbook: National Nutrition Week, 1976, Photos(50), TD(41), Pamphlets(10), Newspaper Clippings, Certificates(8), Newsletters(4) (Box-folder 071:001)
  Letters, Reports, Memorandum